{
  "results": [
    {
      "id": "1794",
      "question": "9 + 8 = ?",
      "selectedAnswer": 17,
      "result": "✅ Correcto"
    },
    {
      "id": "a20e",
      "question": "2 + 8 = ?",
      "selectedAnswer": 10,
      "result": "✅ Correcto"
    },
    {
      "id": "000f",
      "question": "5 - 4 = ?",
      "selectedAnswer": 1,
      "result": "✅ Correcto"
    },
    {
      "id": "3353",
      "question": "1 + 6 = ?",
      "selectedAnswer": 7,
      "result": "✅ Correcto"
    },
    {
      "id": "2343",
      "question": "9 + 5 = ?",
      "selectedAnswer": 16,
      "result": "❌ Incorrecto"
    },
    {
      "id": "d698",
      "question": "5 - 9 = ?",
      "selectedAnswer": -2,
      "result": "❌ Incorrecto"
    },
    {
      "id": "c9b7",
      "question": "5 - 3 = ?",
      "selectedAnswer": 2,
      "result": "✅ Correcto"
    },
    {
      "id": "e367",
      "question": "6 + 8 = ?",
      "selectedAnswer": 12,
      "result": "❌ Incorrecto"
    },
    {
      "id": "3421",
      "question": "10 - 4 = ?",
      "selectedAnswer": 6,
      "result": "✅ Correcto"
    },
    {
      "id": "79fa",
      "question": "8 + 6 = ?",
      "selectedAnswer": 12,
      "result": "❌ Incorrecto"
    },
    {
      "id": "0893",
      "question": "3 * 9 = ?",
      "selectedAnswer": 28,
      "result": "❌ Incorrecto"
    }
  ]
}